Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part III WAG.025.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Departments, Chapters, and Divisions, 1940-2009
  - Subseries A: Anti-Discrimination Department, 1943-1969
    - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations Merger, 1955 (Box 305, Folder 63)
    - AFL-CIO: Subcommittee on Discrimination in Trade Unions, 1955 (Box 305, Folder 64)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1955 (Box 305, Folder 65)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1955 (Box 305, Folder 66)
    - American Immigration Conference, 1955 (Box 305, Folder 67)
    - American Immigration Conference: "News", 1955 (Box 305, Folder 68)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Committee-Anti-Defamation League Joint Memorandums, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - American Jewish Tercentenary, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 3a)
    - American Jewry, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - American Labor Education Service, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - American Labor Services for the U.N., 1955 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - American Legion, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - American Veterans Committee, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - American Zionist Council, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - Anti-Semitism, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 12)
    - Anti-Semitism: US Racist Publications, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 13)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 14)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers: Committee on Personnel Practices, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 15)
    - Automobile Association of America, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 16)
    - Bell, Daniel, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 17)
    - Bill of Rights Day, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 18)
    - Bor'ba (Russian), 1955 (Box 306, Folder 19)
    - Brooklyn Committee for Revision of McCarran-Walter Act, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 20)
    - Brooklyn Human Relations Conference, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 21)
    - Brotherhood of Railway Train Men, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 22)
    - Bureau of Jewish Employment Problems, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 23)
    - California State Federation of Labor, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 24)
    - 'Catholic Interracialist", 1955 (Box 306, Folder 25)
    - Chanin, Nathan, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 26)
    - Civil Liberties: General, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 27)
    - Civil Rights Bill, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 28)
    - Commission on Law and Social Action: Reports, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 29)
    - Committee on JLC Field Staff Operations, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 30)
    - Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 31)
    - Communism, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 32)
    - Communism: Jewish Life, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 33)
    - Community Audits, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 34)
    - Conference of Jewish Organizations, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 35)
    - Confidential, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 36)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 37)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Department of Education, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 38)
    - Connecticut Federation of Labor, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 39)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), New York City, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 40)
    - Corsi, Edward E., 1955 (Box 306, Folder 41)
    - Council Against Intolerance in America, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 42)
    - Council of Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 43)
    - Crank Letters, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 44)
    - Democratic Human Relations Committee, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 45)
    - "Divagando", 1955 (Box 306, Folder 46)
    - Egypt, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 47)
    - Employment, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 48)
    - Employment, Anti-Semitism in, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 49)
    - Equal Job Conference, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 50)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (FEPC), 1955 (Box 306, Folder 51)
    - FEPC: Municipal, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 52)
    - FEPC: State, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 53)
    - Federation Employment and Guidance Service, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 54)
    - Federation of Jewish Philanthropists, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 55)
    - Field Staff: Expenses, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 56)
    - Films, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 57)
    - Finances: Field Offices, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 58)
    - Fisk University, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 59)
    - Fort Monmouth Case, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 60)
    - Fund for the Republic, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 61)
    - Genocide, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 62)
    - Germany, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 63)
    - Goldberg, Arthur, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 64)
    - Government Contracts, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 65)
    - Hate Groups, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 66)
    - Held, Adolph, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 67)
    - Heller, Phil, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 68)
    - Housing, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 69)
    - Houston, TX, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 70)
    - Human Relations, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 71)
    - Immigration, 1955 (Box 306, Folder 72)
    - Immigration: Carnegie Hall Rally, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - Immigration: McCarran-Walter Act, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Immigration: "Notes on Immigrant Care", 1955 (Box 307, Folder 2a)
    - Institutes and Workshops, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Integration of Schools, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - International Electrical Workers, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - International Labor Press, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1955 (Box 307, Folder 9)
    - Inter-University Labor Education Committee, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 10)
    - Israel, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 11)
    - Jacobs, Sam, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 12)
    - JLC: Boston, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 13)
    - JLC: Bridgeport, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 13a)
    - JLC: Chicago, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 14)
    - JLC: Cleveland, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 15)
    - JLC: Detroit, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 16)
    - JLC Day-by-Day Activities, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 17)
    - JLC: Los Angeles, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 18)
    - JLC: Minnesota, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 18a)
    - "JLC News Clips", 1955 (Box 307, Folder 19)
    - JLC Panel on New York City Affairs, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 20)
    - JLC: Philadelphia, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 21)
    - JLC: Pittsburgh, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 22)
    - JLC: San Francisco, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 22a)
    - Jewish Occupational Council, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 23)
    - Jewish War Veterans, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 24)
    - Kaplansky, Kalman, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 25)
    - Karagan, Herbert von: Controversy, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 26)
    - Kaye, Betty, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 27)
    - Kirschenbaum, Walter, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 28)
    - Kissman, Joseph, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 29)
    - Klein, Paul, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 30)
    - Knox, Israel, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 31)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Resolutions, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 32)
    - Labor Conferences, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 33)
    - "Labor Reports", 1955 (Box 307, Folder 34)
    - "Labor's Challenge" (Radio Script), 1955 (Box 307, Folder 35)
    - Large City Budgeting Conference, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 36)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 37)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 38)
    - Liberal Party, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 39)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 40)
    - Loyalty Oath for Jurors, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 41)
    - Major, Robert: Research Proposal re; Immigrant Nazis, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 42)
    - Meany, George, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 43)
    - Memos: CRC's, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 44)
    - Memos: Field Staff, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 45)
    - Memos: Inter-Office, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 46)
    - Michigan CIO, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 47)
    - Middle East, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 48)
    - Minnesota, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 49)
    - Minnesota Jewish Council, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 50)
    - Mississippi, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 51)
    - Mollet, Guy, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 52)
    - Morocco, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 53)
    - Muravchik, Emanuel, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 54)
    - Muravchik, Emanuel: Reports, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 55)
    - Muravchik, Emanuel: Speaking Engagements, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 56)
    - Nassau Human Relations Council, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 57)
    - National Agricultural Workers Union, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 58)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1955 (Box 307, Folder 59)
    - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 60)
    - National Citizens Commission for the Public Schools, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 61)
    - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 62)
    - National Committee for Rural Schools, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 63)
    - National Committee on Immigration and Citizenship, 1955 (Box 307, Folder 64)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC), 1955 (Box 308, Folder 1-2)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Ad Hoc on Four Power Conference and Fate of Jews, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Agenda Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Civil Liberties, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Community Consultation, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Discrimination in Educational Institutions, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 7)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Employment Discrimination, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 9)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Intercultural Education, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 10)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Interreligious Activities, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Executive Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 12)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Finance Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 13)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Immigration Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 14)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Joint Advisory Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 15-17)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Labor Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 18)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Legislative Information Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 19)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Mass Media Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 20)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Membership Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 21)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Motion Picture Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 22)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Reassessment Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 23-24)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Veterans, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 25)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 26)
    - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 27)
    - National Labor Service, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 28)
    - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 29)
    - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 30)
    - National Trade Union Committee for Racial Justice, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 31)
    - National Urban League, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 32)
    - Negro Labor Committee, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 33)
    - New Jersey Department of Education: Division Against Discrimination, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 34)
    - New York Council on Discrimination, 1955 (Box 308, Folder 35)
    - New York State Commission Against Discrimination, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - New York State Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - New York Times, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Panel on New York Civil Rights Affairs, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - Panel: Subcommittee on Employment Discrimination, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - Parkchester, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia Staff Question, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Post War World Council, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - President's Committee on Government Contracts, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - Press Associates-PAI, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 11)
    - Puerto Rico, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 12)
    - Radio Programs, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - Religion and Public Schools, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 14)
    - Reports, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 15)
    - Resolutions, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 16)
    - Right to Work Laws, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 17)
    - RWDSU Record, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco, CA, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 19)
    - Schools: General, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 20)
    - Schools: North, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 21)
    - Schools: Integration (South), 1955 (Box 309, Folder 22)
    - Security Program, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 23)
    - Seligman, Ben: Reports, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 24)
    - Silver, George, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 25)
    - "Social Order", 1955 (Box 309, Folder 26)
    - Socialist International, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 27)
    - Socialist Party, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 28)
    - Staff Biographies, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 29)
    - Staff Meetings, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 30)
    - Steelworkers; Conference on Human Relations, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 31)
    - Subventions, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 32)
    - Taft, Philip, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 33)
    - Telegrams, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 34)
    - Tennessee Society to Maintain Segregation, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 34a)
    - Till, Emmet Case, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 35)
    - Union for Democratic Socialism, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 36)
    - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 37)
    - United Automobile Workers (UAW), 1955 (Box 309, Folder 38)
    - UAW-CIO, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 39)
    - UAW: Fair Practiced Department, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 40)
    - United Hebrew Traders, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 41)
    - United Housing Foundation, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 42)
    - United Nations, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 43)
    - United Steelworkers of America, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 44)
    - University of Wisconsin School for Workers, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 45)
    - Unsigned Leaflet, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 46)
    - Vermont, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 47)
    - Vorspan, Al, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 48)
    - Worthy, Bill, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 49)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 50)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 51)
    - Workmen's Circle: English-Speaking Division, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 52)
    - Workers Defense League, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 53)
    - Workers Education Bureau, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 54)
    - Women's Trade Union League, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 55)
    - Young Socialist League, 1955 (Box 309, Folder 56)
    - Zimmerman, Charles S., 1955 (Box 309, Folder 57)
    - AAA Regional Cases and Action, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 58)
    - American Association for United Nations, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 59)
    - American Automobile Club, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 60)
    - American Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 61)
    - American Council for Judaism, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 62)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 63)
    - American Federation of International Institutes, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 64)
    - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Cope, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 65)
    - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 66)
    - AFL-CIO Conference on Federal Aid to Education, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 67)
    - AFL-CIO "Education News and Views", 1956 (Box 309, Folder 68)
    - AFL-CIO Free Trade Union News, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 69)
    - AFL-CIO Subcommittee on Discrimination in Trade Unions, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 70)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 71)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 72)
    - AFSCME, Local 1707, 1956 (Box 309, Folder 73)
    - American Committee on United Europe, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - American Immigration Conference, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - American Jewish Committee – Anti-Defamation League Joint Memorandums, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - American Labor Education Service, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - American Legion, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 8)
    - American Museum of Immigration, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - American Veterans Committee, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - American Zionist Council, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Anti-Defamation League- Jewish Labor Committee, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 15)
    - Anti-Semitism U.S., 1956 (Box 310, Folder 16)
    - Arab Discrimination Against American Jews, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 17)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 18)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers: Committee on Personnel Practices, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 19)
    - Automobile Association of America, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 20)
    - Baida Case, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 21)
    - Barbash, Jack, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 22)
    - Bell, Daniel, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 23)
    - Birmingham, AL, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 24)
    - Bor'ba (Russian), 1956 (Box 310, Folder 25)
    - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 26)
    - Buffalo: Board of Community Relations, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 27)
    - Bureau on Jewish Employment Problems, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 28)
    - California Federation of Labor, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 29)
    - Canadian Labor Congress, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 30)
    - Confidential, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 31)
    - Chanin, Herschell, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 32)
    - Christian Labor Association, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 33)
    - Citizens Committee for Civil Rights, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 34)
    - Civil Rights General, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 35)
    - Civil Rights Steering Committee, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Civil Rights in Manhattan, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 37)
    - Communist Activities, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 38)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Atlanta, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 39)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Boston, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 40)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Brooklyn, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 41)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Cincinnati, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 42)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Cleveland, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 43)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Detroit, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 44)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Essex County, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 45)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Houston, 1956 (Box 310, Folder 46)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Indiana, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Kansas City, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Los Angeles, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Miami, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Milwaukee, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Minnesota, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): New Jersey, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Philadelphia, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Pittsburgh, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 9)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): San Francisco, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 10)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): St. Louis, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 11)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Washington, DC, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 12)
    - Conference of NYC Jewish Agencies on the South, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 13)
    - Conference on Jewish Social Studies, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 14)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1956 (Box 311, Folder 15)
    - Consultative Conference on Desegregation, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 16)
    - Conventions, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 17)
    - Council of Jewish Federations, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 18)
    - Courts, Gus, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 19)
    - Crank Letters, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 20)
    - Education: Powell Amendment, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 21)
    - Egyptian: Protests on Treatment, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 22)
    - Egyptian Jews: Reports, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 23)
    - Fact Sheet, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 24)
    - Fact Sheet: Middle East Conflict, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 25)
    - Fact Sheet: Labor in the Middle East, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 26)
    - Fair Employment Practice Commission (FEPC), 1956 (Box 311, Folder 27)
    - Fair Employment Practice Commission (FEPC): Municipal, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 28)
    - Fair Employment Practice Commission (FEPC): Survey, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 29)
    - Federation Employment and Guidance Service, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 30)
    - Field Staff Problems, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 31)
    - Films, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 32)
    - Fisher, Bernice, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 33)
    - Fisk, University, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 34)
    - Ford Foundation, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 35)
    - Free Europe Committee, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 36)
    - Fund for the Republic, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 37)
    - Fund Raising Letters, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 38)
    - Germany SDP, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 39)
    - Harvard Crimson: Special Supplement on Civil Rights, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 39A)
    - Held, Adolph, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 40)
    - Hill, Herbert, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 41)
    - Histadrut, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 42)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Employees … Union, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 43)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Strike in Miami, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 44)
    - Human Rights: Bibliography, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 45)
    - Hungary, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 46)
    - Huth, Arno, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 47)
    - Immigration, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 48)
    - Immigration: Legislation, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 48a)
    - "In Friendship", 1956 (Box 311, Folder 49)
    - Institute on Jewish Affairs, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 50)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 51)
    - International Labor Organization (ILO), 1956 (Box 311, Folder 52)
    - ILO Discrimination in Employment, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 53)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 54)
    - Israel, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 55)
    - JLC: Communications to Field Staff, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 56)
    - JLC: General, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - JLC: Reports, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 2-3)
    - JLC: Day–by-Day Activities, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - "JLC News Clips", 1956 (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Kaye, Betty, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - Labor and Civil Rights, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 7)
    - Labor and Civil Rights (case histories), 1956 (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Resolutions, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Labor Conferences, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Lehman, Senator Herbert, 1956 (Box 312, Folder 12)
    - Lerman, Louis E., 1956 (Box 312, Folder 13)